전사들이여
Fellow warriors,
나는 정복자 쉘도르다.
this is Sheldor the Conqueror.
이제 곧 애시더스의 요새로 향하겠다
We are about to enter
Axidus' fortress.
오랜 전투가 될 것이니
모두 방광을 다시 한 번 확인하도록
Now, this is a long run,
so let's do another bladder check.
배리, 이번에도 기다릴 텐데
꼭 병원 한 번 가봐
OK, Barry,
we'll wait for you again,
but you really should see a doctor.
쉘도르는 잠시 잠수타겠다
Sheldor is AFK.
페니, 지금 어려움을 겪고 있나요?
Are you experiencing
some sort of difficulty?
네, 문을 못 열겠어요
Yes. I can't get
my stupid door open.
지금 자동차 열쇠를 끼운 건
알고 있는 건가요?
You appear to have put
your car key in the door lock,
are you aware of that?
당연하죠
그렇다면 이만
All right, then.
젠장!
Damn it.
좀 더 조용히 할 수도 있나요?
Would it be possible for you
to do this a little more quietly?
망할 열쇠가 안 빠져요
I can't get
the damn key out.
당연하죠, 페니 문에 달린 볼드윈 자물쇠는
전형적인 가장자리 부착형 실린더인데
It's not surprising--
that Baldwin lock on your door
uses traditional
edge-mounted cylinders,
페니 폭스바겐 열쇠는
중앙 실린더용이니까요
whereas the key for your Volkswagen
uses a center cylinder system.
고마워요, 쉘든
Thank you.
천만에요
You're welcome.
궁금한 건요, 왜 자동차 열쇠를
문에 끼운 거예요?
Point of inquiry: why did you put
your car key in the door lock?
왜냐고요?
오늘 오디션이 있대서
Why?
Because today I had an audition,
it took me two hours to get there,
두 시간 걸려서 갔더니
제 차례까지 한 시간이나 기다리고
I waited an hour for my turn,
and before I could even start,
시작하기도 전에 배역을 맡기엔
너무 중서부 느낌이라고 하더군요
they told me I looked
too Midwest for the part.
중서부 느낌이라니
도대체 뭐하자는 거예요?
Too Midwest.
What the hell does that even mean?
미국 중서부 지방에는 스칸디나비아와
독일계 사람들이 많이 거주하죠
The American Midwest was mostly settled
by Scandinavian and Germanic people.
- 특징적인 광대뼈와..
- 무슨 말인지는 알아요!
They have a characteristic
facial bone...
I know what it means!
LA에 온 지 벌써 2년 가까이 됐는데
God! I have been in L.A.
for almost two years now,
단 한 번도 연기는 못했어요
and I haven't gotten
a single acting job.
아무것도 해낸 게 없어요
I've accomplished nothing,
가게에서 월급을 올려준 것도 아니고
6달 동안 남자랑 못 잤고
haven't gotten any raise at work,
haven't even had sex in 6 months,
그리고 방금 계단 올라오는데
and just now,
when I was walking up those stairs,
파리가 입속으로 날아와서 삼켜버렸다고요
a fly flew in my mouth
and I ate it!
곤충은 많은 문화권에서 주식이에요
Actually, insects are a dietary staple
in many cultures.
거의 단백질 100%예요
They're almost pure protein.
제기랄!
Oh, son of a bitch!
냉동식품 표면에 응결된 물방울들로
봉지의 구조가 약해졌나 보군요
I believe the condensation
on your frozen foods
weakened the structural
integrity of the bag.
열쇠의 수수께끼로 돌아가면
But returning to your key conundrum,
perhaps you should call a locksmith
열쇠 수리공을 불러서
문을 열어달라고 하는 게 좋겠네요
- and have him open the door for you.
- I did.
이미 했죠
여기 오게 되면 온다고 하더군요
He said he'll get here
when he gets here.
아무 의미 없는 동어 반복 때문에
화가 난 거군요?
You're frustrated
because he phrased his reply
in the form
of a meaningless tautology?
아니에요! 모든 일에
전 실패만 해서 화가 난 거예요
I am frustrated because
I am a failure at everything
게다가 입에서 파리 냄새가 난다고요
and my breath smells like fly.
자, 자..
There, there.
우리 집에서 기다리고 싶어요?
Would you prefer to wait
in our apartment?
아뇨, 여기 냉동식품 널브러진 바닥에서
3살짜리 애처럼 우는 게 낫겠어요
No, I'd rather sit
on this freezing-cold floor
sobbing like a three-year-old.
그렇다면, 이만
All right, then.
진짜 못 살아
For God's sake.
방금 비꼬는 방법을 터득한 것 같군
Just when I think
I've gotten the hang of sarcasm.
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(club.nate.com/24)
수정 금지 / 자유 배포
피드백은 메일로 보내주세요
동영상 정보
175MB / HDTV-LOL
영문자막
forom.com
한글교정 우채우(shinhwanl@nate.com)
싱크편집 / 한글번역
현준호(lightinstom@nate.com)
The Big Bang Theory
2x03 The Barbarian Sublimation
Original Air Date on CBS
Oct. 5, 2008
Subtitles:
sub-way.fr / seriessub.com / forom.com
편하게 있어요
Make yourself comfortable.
거긴 말고요
Not there.
쉘도르가 돌아왔다
Sheldor is back online.
쉘도르요?
Sheldor?
정복자예요
The Conqueror.
뭐 하는 거예요?
What are you doing?
잠수
AFK.
로버트 E.하워드의 원작
"코난, 더 바바리안"의 세계관을 바탕으로 한
I'm playing Age of Conan,
an online multiplayer game
set in the universe of
Robert E. Howard's Conan the Barbarian.
"에이지 오브 코난"이라는
온라인 게임 중이에요
쉘도르 왔음
Sheldor back online.
- 잠수가 뭐예요?
- 잠수
- What's "AFK"?
- AFK.
키보드에서 멀어진다고요
Away From Keyboard.
알겠어요
Oh, I see.
그게 무슨 의미죠?
What does that stand for?
알겠다고요
Oh, I see.
그래요, 그게 무슨 말이냔 말이에요
(OIC로 잘못 알아들은 쉘든)
Yes, but what does
it stand for?
마법이 부여된 신발을 누르면 장비가 돼요
Just click on the enchanted boots
to put them on.
흠.. 다른 색 신발은 없을까요?
I don't know--
can I see them in another color?
그냥 눌러요
Just click on them.
축하해요, 이제 3레벨 전사네요
Congratulations.
You are now a level-three warrior.
- 뭐 하고 있어요?
- 레너드, 전 이제 3레벨 전사예요
- What's going on?
- Guess what? I'm a level-three warrior.
대단하네요, 지금 복도에
장본 것들 널려 있는 거 알아요?
Great.
Do you know there are groceries
outside of your apartment?
아이스크림이 녹아서 야생 동물들을
끌어들이고 있어서 말한 거예요
I only bring it up because
your ice cream's melting
and it's starting
to attract wildlife.
정글에 있을까요
해변으로 갈까요?
Do I stay in the jungle
or go towards the beach?
아무 상관없어요
지금은 보물을 찾아요
It doesn't matter-- right now;
you're looking for treasure.
- 어디 가는 거예요!
- 지금 잘하고 있어요
- Wait, where are you going?
- No, no. You're okay.
악어를 만나면
신발로 차버려요
If you run into crocodiles,
just kick them with your boots.
어떻게 된 건지 말해줄래?
You want to catch me up?
어디 보자..
Well, let's see,
자동차 열쇠로 아파트 문을 열려고 했어
she attempted to open
her apartment with her car key
얼굴이 과하게 중서부 사람들처럼 생겼거든
because her face
is overly Midwestern...
6달 동안 남자랑 못 잤고
she hasn't had sex in six months...
파리를 먹었대
and she ate a fly.
진짜야? 6달씩이나?
Seriously?
Six months?
어머나! 보물 상자다!
난 이제 부자야!
Oh, my God!
A treasure chest! I'm rich!
3레벨인데 부자인 줄 알아
Level three,
and she thinks she's rich.
초보들이란..
What a newb.
- 준비 다 됐어
- 한번 놀아보실까
We're all set.
Let her rip.
이거 봐요
옥수수 전분이랑 물로만 만든 거예요
Check it out--
it's just corn starch and water.
액체이면서도 스피커와의 충돌로 고체 성질을 지니는
They make up a non-Newtonian fluid,
which is liquid,
비뉴턴형 유체가 된 거죠
but solid under the percussive
action of the speaker.
같이 펑키를 느껴봐요
That's what makes it get all funky.
잠시만요, 쉘든이랑 할 얘기가 있어요
Listen, I need to talk to Sheldon.
아니, 페니가 쉘든이라고 말한 거 맞아
No, that's what she said--
Sheldon.
게임을 사서 토르티지 섬을 돌아다녔는데
I bought the game, and I've been
exploring the island of Tortage,
경비 대장을 어떻게 넘겨야 할지 모르겠어요
but I don't know
how to get past the Guard Captain.
- 마법검은 가지고 있어요?
- 아뇨, 지금 청동 단검인데요
- Do you have the Enchanted Sword?
- No, I have a bronze dagger.
청동 단검으로는 경비 대장 못 깨요
You can't slay the Guard
with a bronze dagger.
지금 이건 대문에
열쇠 넣는 거랑 다를 게 없잖아요
My Lord, it's like the car key
in your apartment door all over again.
- 알겠어요, 그 칼은 어떻게 구해요?
- 미트라 사원에는 갔어요?
- All right, how do I get the sword?
- Have you been to the Temple of Mitra?
언덕 위에 이상한 사제들이 있던 곳이요?
Is that the place on the hill
with the weird priest in front of it?
- 아뇨, 어디냐면.. 줘봐요
- 정말 고마워요
- It's... Oh, for God's sakes, gimme.
- Thank you-- I really appreciate.
이런 건 혼자서도 할 줄 알아야 해요
You're gonna have to learn
to do these things for yourself.
잘난 척하지 말고 칼이나 찾아봐요
Don't patronize me--
just get the sword!
도대체 뭔 일이래?
What the frack?
그러니까, 어제도 둘이서 밤새면서 했다니깐
Beats me.
They were playing all last night, too.
조잡한 만화책 크로스오버 같잖아
It's like some kind
of weird comic book crossover.
헐크가 페퍼민트 패티랑
데이트하는 것처럼 말이야
Like if Hulk were dating
Peppermint Patty.
페퍼민트 패티는 레즈비언인 줄 알았는데
I always thought
Peppermint Patty was a lesbian.
아니, 마시가 레즈비언이고
No, that's Marcie.
페퍼민트 패티는 그냥 운동선수야
Peppermint Patty's just athletic.
여기요, 마법검이에요
There you go--
one Enchanted Sword.
어서 줘요, 경비 대장 죽여버려야지
All right, gimme, gimme.
I want to kill the Guard Captain.
저 여자 똑바로 좀 살라고 해
That girl needs to get a life.
쉘든
위험! 위험!
Danger! Danger!
안 위험해요, 페니예요
No danger-- it's just me, Penny.
Listen, I got to level 25
25레벨이 돼서 보라색 연꽃 늪에 갔거든요
and reached Purple Lotus Swamp.
제 침실에 있잖아요
You're in my bedroom.
- 레너드가 비상 열쇠 맡겼거든요
- 제 침실에는 아무도 못 들어와요
- Leonard gave me an emergency key.
- People can't be in my bedroom.
- 그럼 거실에서 이야기할까요?
- 잠옷 바지 안 입고 있어요
- Can we go talk in the living room?
- I'm not wearing pajama bottoms.
- 왜요?
- 포도 주스를 흘렸거든요
- Why not?
- I spilled grape juice.
그럼 다른 잠옷 입어요
Wear different pajamas.
안 돼요, 이게 월요일 잠옷이에요
I can't wear different pajamas--
these are my Monday pajamas.
제 침실에는 아무도 못 들어와요
People cannot be in my bedroom.
알았어요, 암흑성 퀘스트를 하기에는
너무 빠른지 대답만 해줘요
Fine, just tell me, is it too soon
to join a quest to the Black Castle?
누가 암흑성 퀘스트 같이 하재요?
You were invited on a quest
to the Black Castle?
부다페스트에 사는 어떤 사람들이요
By some guys in Budapest.
제 캐릭터가 제대로 행동하는 건지
확신이 안 서서요
I'm just not sure it's the right move
for my character.
당연히 아니죠
이제 고작 25레벨이에요
Of course it's not--
you're only a level 25.
그 헝가리인들이 페니를
드래곤 먹이로 이용하려는 거예요
These Hungarians, they're just
using you for dragon fodder.
진짜요? 쉘든이라면 헝가리 야만인 무리를
믿을 수 있을 거라고 생각했는데요
Really? Boy, you'd think you could trust
a horde of Hungarian barbarians.
제발요, 페니
전 자야 해요
Please, Penny, enough.
I have to sleep.
잘했어요, 고마워요
Okay, you were great.
Thanks.
쉘든 방에는 들어가지 마세요
지금 바지를 안 입고 있거든요
Listen, don't go in Sheldon's room.
He's not wearing bottoms.
쉘든, 어떻게 된 건지 또 말해줄래?
Sheldon, you want
to catch me up again?
전 오늘 아주 바빠요
People, I'm very busy today.
학장님, 그건 압니다만
I realize that, Dr. Gablehauser,
학과 내에서 발생한 분쟁을
조정하는 것도 학장님의 일이니까요
but it's your job,
as head of the department,
to mediate
all interdepartmental disputes.
대학 정책 편람 4장 2절에
"학과 내 분쟁 조정"이 있죠
University Policy Manual,
Chapter Four, Subsection Two:
"Mediation
of Interdepartmental Disputes."
알겠어요, 윙클 박사, 쿠퍼 박사에게
이번에는 어떻게 불렀나요?
Fine.
Dr. Winkle, what colorful name
did you call Dr. Cooper this time?
머저리 박사요
Dr. Dumb-Ass.
쿠퍼 박사, 윙클 박사가 사과할 겁니다
Dr. Cooper,
Dr. Winkle apologizes.
- 안 합니다
- 할 리가 없죠
- I don't.
- She doesn't.
버크만 204호의 본체는
제가 쓰기로 분명히 계약이 되었는데
Here's the problem.
I was clearly signed up
to use the mainframe in Buckman 204,
윙클 박사가 계약서를 계속 찢는 겁니다
and Dr. Winkle just wantonly
ripped the sign-up sheet off the wall.
정식 계약서도 아니에요
It wasn't an official sign-up sheet.
He printed it himself,
자기가 직접 출력해서 6개월마다
자기 이름 써넣는 것뿐이라고요
and he put his name down
on every slot for the next 6 months.
대학의 재원이 하찮은 야생 거위나
쫓는 데 쓰이는 것이 아니라면
If it is a crime to ensure
that the university's resources
are not being squandered
chasing subatomic wild geese,
저도 잘못을 인정하죠
then I plead guilty.
페니?
- Penny!
- Do you need to get that, Dr. Cooper?
- 전화받아야 하나요, 쿠퍼 박사?
- 절대 안 받아요
God, no.
그렇다고 꺼놓지는 마
노벨 위원회에서 너한테 할 전화를 못 받잖아
Don't turn it off, you might miss
your call from the Nobel committee
올해의 머저리 후보에 올랐다고 할 텐데 말이야
telling you you've been nominated
as Dumb-Ass Laureate of the Year.
그래?
Oh, yeah? Well...
넌 후보로 지명되는 일조차 없을 걸
you wouldn't even be nominated.
학장님, 전 지금 중요한 계산과
시뮬레이션할 게 넘칩니다
Dr. Gablehauser, I have a series
of important calculations
and simulations to run.
윙클 박사가 하는 건 쓸데없는
데이터 붙들고 남을 놀리기나.. / 잠시만요
All she's doing is
reducing irrelevant data
- and making a mock...
- Excuse me.
게이블하우저입니다
쿠퍼 박사 전화군요
It's for you.
여보세요
페니, 지금은 전화 못 받아요
Penny, this is not a good time.
불타는 영혼의 성소에
갈 정도가 아니라고 말했잖아요
No, I told you,
you're not prepared
for the Sanctum of Burning Souls.
그 퀘스트를 하려면 적어도 5명에
그 중 한 명은 35레벨 성직자여야 해요
You need to be in a group
of at least 5 for that quest
and one should be
a level 35 healer.
지금은 접속 못해요
I can't log on and help you.
집에 가면 이야기해요
We'll talk when I get home.
제가 컴퓨터를 더 쓸 수는 없게 되는 거죠?
I'm not getting
the computing time, am I?
머저리
Dumb-ass.
레너드, 페니 좀 어떻게 해
Leonard, you have to do
something about Penny.
내 수면을 방해하고
내 일도 방해하고
She is interfering with my sleep,
she's interfering with my work,
내 삶에 또 다른 중요한 일이 있으면
그 일도 방해할 게 분명해
and if I had another significant
aspect of my life,
I'm sure she'd be interfering
with that, too.
왜 내가 해야 해?
온라인 게임 가르쳐준 건 너잖아
Why should I do something?
You introduced her to online gaming.
그렇지만 이사 왔을 때
처음 인사한 건 너잖아
Yes, but you're the one who said hello
to her when she moved in.
네가 너를 단속했더라면
이런 일은 일어나지 않았을 거야
If you'd simply restrained yourself,
none of this would be happening.
- 그냥 연락하지 말라고 말해
- 당연히 했지
- Just tell her to leave you alone.
- I did, I told her,
말도 하고, 문자도 보내고
트위터에도 강조해서 써놨어
I texted her, I sent out
a very emphatic twitter.
페이스북에는 어떻게 써놨냐면
I even changed my Facebook
status to
"쉘든 쿠퍼는 페니가
연락하지 않기를 바랍니다"라고 해놨어
"Sheldon Cooper wishes Penny
would leave him alone."
더는 어떻게 해야 할지 모르겠어
I don't know what else to do.
- 그렇다고 나보고 어떻게 하란 거야?
- 나도 몰라
- Well, what am I supposed to do?
- I don't know,
그렇지만 어떻게든 하지 않으면, 경고하건대
but if you don't figure something out,
I warn you,
같이 살기 정말 힘들어질 거야
I shall become
very difficult to live with.
그럼 지금까지는 즐겁고 행복한
쉘든이었단 말이야?
You mean up until now
we've been experiencing
the happy, fun-time Sheldon?
- 그래
- 내가 얘기해 볼게
- Yes.
- I'll go talk to her.
아니, 프리츠, 내 옆으로 와요
No, Fritz, I need you on my flank.
독일어 몰라요
Flanken sie, flanken sie.
No, I don't know German.
- 페니, 안녕하세요
- 바빠요
- Hey, Penny.
- Busy.
그래 보이네요
오늘 일 안 해요?
Yeah, I see that.
Shouldn't you be at work?
월요일에는 쉬어요
I don't work on Mondays.
오늘 목요일이에요
It's Thursday.
- 페니, 있잖아요..
- 페넬로페 여왕 잠수, 왜요?
- Listen, Penny...
- Queen Penelope, AFK. What...?
할 말이 뭐냐면요
Here's the thing.
착한 사람들도 말이죠
이런 게임을 하다 보면
Sometimes people,
good people,
start playing these games
and they find themselves,
게임에 중독되거든요
일부러 그런 건 아니더라도요
through no fault of their own,
kind of... addicted.
요점만 말해요
이제 레벨업할 때 다 됐거든요
Get to the point.
I'm about to level up here.
실제 인생에서 성취감을
느끼지 못한 사람들은
If a person doesn't have a sense
of achievement in their real life,
거짓 성취감을 느낄 수 있는
가상 세계에 쉽게 빠지게 되죠
it's easy to lose themselves
in a virtual world
where they can get a false
sense of accomplishment.
재잘재잘..
페넬로페 여왕 돌아왔음
Yeah, jabber, jabber.
Boys, Queen Penelope's back online.
페니..
Penny, you've got...
머리에 과자 붙었어요
Cheetos in your hair.
고마워요
Thanks.
페니, 레너드예요
Hey, Penny, it's me again, Leonard.
지금은 안 된다고 했잖아요
I said not now.
페니가 걱정 돼서 그런 거예요
I know, I'm just a little
concerned about you.
지금은 안 된댔죠!
I said not now!
알았어요, 나중에 얘기해요
Okay, maybe later.
Hey, guys.
- 얘 왜 이래?
- 페니 때문에 밤에 잠을 못 잤어
- What's with him?
- Penny's been keeping him up at night.
나도 그래
Me, too.
물론 다른 방식으로겠지만
But probably in a different way.
"에이지 오브 코난"에 완전 빠졌어
쉬지도 않고 게임한다니깐
She's gotten really
hooked on Age of Conan.
- She's playing nonstop.
- Yes, online gaming addiction.
온라인 게임 중독이구나
멀티 플레이 하는 원숭이가
등에 달라붙는 것보다는 괜찮을 거야
There's nothing worse than having
that multi-player monkey on your back.
- 쉘든, 일어나!
- 위험! 위험!
- Sheldon, wake up!
- Danger! Danger!
안녕, 친구들
Afternoon, men.
쉘든
성인 남성에서 날 제외해서
유치한 듯 만들려는 네 의도는
Your attempt at juvenilizing me
by excluding me from the set
of adult males, just...
너무 피곤해서 말도 안 나와
I'm too tired to do this.
바비 인형이랑 밤샌다는 이야기는 들었어
I heard you've been pulling all-nighters
with Middle Earth Barbie.
내 방에 오잖아
아무도 내 방에 오면 안 돼
She comes into my room.
No one's supposed to be in my room.
성적 불만에 대한 보상을 위해
온라인으로 도피했다고 생각해
I would postulate that she's escaping
into the online world
to compensate
for her sexual frustration.
나도 그래
I do that, too.
물론 다른 방식으로겠지만
But probably in a different way.
페니는 그래서 그런 거 아니야
That's not what she's doing, Leslie.
남은 자존심을 지키려고 그러는 거야
She's just trying to shore up
her self-esteem.
- 섹스랑은 아무 상관없어
- 모든 건 섹스랑 연결돼 있어
- It has nothing to do with sex.
- Everything has to do with sex.
증명해봐
Testify.
그 손은 안 만져
I'm not touching that.
너무 많이 나갔어, 레즐리
You are way off base here.
레너드, 잠시만
Hang on.
내가 레즐리를 과학자나
사람으로 존중하는 건 아니지만
While I have no respect
for Leslie as a scientist
or a human being,
for that matter,
난잡함과 싸구려의 달인인
레즐리의 의견을 인정하지 않을 순 없지
we have to concede her
undeniable expertise
in the interrelated fields
of promiscuity and general sluttiness.
고마워
Thank you.
내 생각엔 그 팅커벨에게 뭔가 필요해
My point is that Tinkerbell
just needs to get her some.
뭘?
Some what?
성교 말이지
Yes, some sexual intercourse.
그건 내가 해줄게
I'll take the bullet.
잠시만, 지금 말하는 건 전부 말도 안 돼
Excuse me,
this whole idea is insane.
토론은 그만
이제 행동에 옮기겠어
Enough debate,
I'm going to take action.
잠시만요
Excuse me.
혹시 지금 성적인 관계를 맺고 계신가요?
Are you currently involved
in a sexual relationship?
아뇨
그런 관계를 원하시나요?
Would you like to be?
당연하죠
Sure, why not?
쉘든
전화번호 주실래요?
Can I have your phone number?
문제 해결이야
There. Problem solved.
머저리 같으니라고
Dumb-ass.
좋아, 지금 고대의 보물창고 문 앞이에요
Okay, I'm at the gate
of the Treasury of the Ancients.
- 이제 들어가요
- 벽에 딱 붙어요
- I'm going in.
- Stay close to the wall.
- 미라는 피해가요
- 알겠어요
- Avoid the mummies.
- Got it.
23살 여자치고 정말 게임을 잘하네요
I must say you're playing very well
for a woman of 23.
- 22이에요
- 네, 22살이요
- Twenty-two.
- Right, 22.
미라들이 왔어요
Here come the mummies.
Which spell do I use,
어느 주문을 써야 하죠?
증오의 타격이랑 광분 중에서요
the hateful strike
or the frenzy stance?
다른 동료들은요?
What happened to your group?
버렸어요, 겁쟁이들뿐이잖아요
I dumped them,
they're a bunch of wussies.
- 광분을 써요
- 광분, 광분, 광분!!
- Frenzy stance.
- Frenzy, frenzy, frenzy!
페니, 있잖아요
So, listen,
페니가 원하는 이상적인 휴가는
would you describe
your ideal vacation
알려지지 않은 땅으로의 거친 모험이에요
집에서 좋은 책을 읽는 거예요?
as a wild adventure
to unknown lands
or staying at home curled up
with a good book?
- 네?
- 시장 조사 중이거든요
- What?
- These are market research questions.
페니가 하는 게임 등록하는 데 쓰는 중이에요
I'm filling out the online
registration for your game.
거친 모험이요
Okay, wild adventure.
광분이 안 먹히잖아요
죽어라, 미라들아, 죽어!
Frenzy stance isn't working.
Die, you undead mummy, die!
- 회복 포션 마셔요
- 고마워요 / 천만에요
- Healing potion.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
1부터 5까지 기준이 나뉘는데
Anyhow, on a scale
of one to five,
1이 남자가 시작하는 것이고
5는 페니가 시작하는 거라면
with one being
always initiated by him
and five being
always initiated by you,
페니는 어떤 방식으로
만남이 이뤄졌으면 좋겠어요?
how do you prefer
your sexual encounters to begin?
- 그런 게 등록 절차에 있어요?
- 네, 꽤 구체적이죠
- That's on the registration?
- Yes, it's quite extensive.
그래도 이걸 다 작성하면
공짜 확장팩을 받을 수 있어요
But if we complete it,
you get a free expansion pack.
퀘스트도 75개 추가되고요
75 additional quests.
멋진데요! 시작은 무조건 저예요
전 별 다섯짜리거든요
Awesome. I totally like to initiate.
I'm a big ol' five.
잘 알겠어요
Good to know.
별 다섯이라
Big ol' five.
- 안녕하세요
레너드, 이쪽은 톰이야
Leonard, this is Tom.
톰, 안녕하세요
쉘든..
Hi, Tom. Sheldon...
아까 식당에서 실수한 것에 대해서
내가 설명해줬잖아
Didn't I explain to you
about your little mistake
in the cafeteria?
확실하게 설명해줬어
같이 있던 다른 사람들도 그랬고
You were very clear.
As was everyone else at the table.
그렇지만 톰은 과학에 따라서 선택된
페니에게 적합한 짝이야
Tom, however,
has been chosen by science
as a suitable mate for Penny.
과학에 따라 선택돼?
Chosen by science?
데이트 사이트에서 쓰는 과학 말이지
Well, what passes for science
on dating sites.
귀납적 알고리즘을 쓴다고는 하지만
They claim to use
heuristic algorithms,
뭐, 헛소리겠지
but it may well be hokum.
페니 보고 데이트 사이트 가입하라고 한 거야?
You got Penny to sign up
for online dating?
당연히 아니지
No, of course not.
계략과 속임수를 썼지
See, I used trickery and deceit.
예감이 안 좋아
This is bad.
톰은 소방서 의료 보조원인데
Tom is a paramedic
with the fire department,
밤에는 의대를 다니고 있어
but he's going to med school at night.
야외 활동을 좋아하고
섹스를 이끌어주는 강한 여성을 좋아해
He likes the outdoors
and strong women
who initiate sex.
정말 안 좋아
Really, really bad.
네가 페니랑 안 되다니 놀랐어
I'm surprised
you struck out with Penny.
알고 보니 페니는 별 다섯짜리더라고
Apparently,
she's a big ol' five.
쉘든, 무슨 일이에요?
- Sheldon, what do you want?
- Good,
제가 남긴 메모를 봤군요
여기 톰이랑 인사해요
you got my note.
I'd like you to meet Tom.
페니, 톰이에요
Penny, this is Tom.
톰, 이쪽은 페니예요
Tom, may I present Penny.
- 안녕하세요
- 네,
- Hi, Penny.
- Yeah, hi. Listen,
여기 온 김에 물어보죠
초보들이랑 퀘스트 진행 중인데
as long as I'm here,
I'm on a quest with a bunch of newbs.
암살자랑 마법사 셋에 몸빵이 없어요
We've got one assassin,
3 spell casters and no tank.
- 나중에 이야기하면 안 될까요?
- 아뇨, 지금 이야기해요
- Can we talk about this later?
- No, no. I need you now.
여기 수동적인 성생활에 야외활동을 좋아하는
톰이랑 이야기해보는 건 어때요?
Wouldn't you prefer
to socialize with Tom,
who is a sexually passive
outdoorsman?
됐어요, 내가 알아서 하죠
Whatever.
I'll figure it out myself.
가요
Bye, Penny.
사진에 나온 모습이랑 완전 딴판이네요
I'm sorry, dude, she didn't look
anything like her picture.
인터넷이 뭐 그렇죠
They never do.
- 안녕하십니까
- 누구죠?
- Hello, fair Penny.
- Who are you?
왈로위츠의 하워드 경입니다
It is I, Sir Howard of Wolowitz.
욘 가상 주점에서 에일 한 잔 하면서
오후 동안 정신적인 탐구를 해 볼까요?
Can I interest you
in an afternoon of spirited questing
followed by a flagon of ale
at Yon Virtual Tavern?
좋아요
Yeah, sure, why not?
어머나, 누가 좀 말려줘
Oh, my God, I need help.
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(club.nate.com/24)
수정 금지 / 자유 배포
피드백은 메일로 보내주세요